teamsideline.com 2011-06-04

# League Management, Registration, Scheduling, and Communication - TeamSideline.com

**1\. Completely IT Respects Your Privacy**  
This TeamSideline Site is owned and operated by Completely IT, a California Corporation. Completely IT respects your privacy. This Privacy Statement informs you of our privacy practices and of the choices you can make about the way your information is collected online and how that information is used. This statement is available on our home page and at the bottom of every TeamSideline Web page. 

**2\. Collection Of Personal Information**  
On TeamSideline, when you register we will ask you to provide personal information which may include your name, address, zip code, telephone number, email address, date of birth, gender, user ID and password. In addition to the information you provide, Completely IT may also collect information during your visit to TeamSideline using Automatic Data Collection Tools, such as cookies, embedded Web links, and other commonly used information-gathering tools. These tools collect certain standard information that your browser sends to our Site such as your browser type and language, access times, and the address of the Site from which you arrived at a Completely IT Site. They may also collect information about your Internet Protocol (IP) address, and clickstream behavior (i.e. the pages you view, the links you click, and other actions you take in connection with Completely IT Sites). An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the Web, allowing Web servers to locate and identify your computer. Computers use IP addresses to communicate on the Internet, allowing users to browse, visit and use web sites. 

**3\. How We Use Your Information**  
The information Completely IT collects helps Completely IT deliver a consistent and personalized experience. For example, Completely IT may use your information to  
• increase the security of your log in process and therefore the security of your information;   
• personalize your TeamSideline experience;  
• provide service and support;   
• update you on new Completely IT services and benefits. 

**4\. How We Share Your Information**  
Completely IT will not sell, rent or lease your personal information to others. Completely IT will not share the personal information you provide to Completely IT with any third parties without your permission, unless to: (i) respond to duly authorized information requests of governmental authorities; (ii) comply with any law, regulation, subpoena, or court order; (iii) help prevent fraud or to enforce or protect the rights and properties of Completely IT or its subsidiaries; or (iv) protect the personal safety of Completely IT employees and third parties on Completely IT property.

**5\. Children's Privacy**  
Completely IT does not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13 and does not target its Sites to children under 13. We encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children’s online activities and interests. 

**6\. Completely IT General Communications**   
Completely IT general communications provide information about products, services, and/or support. This may include new Completely IT product information, special offers, or invitations to participate in market research. 

**7\. Access To And Accuracy Of Your Information**  
Completely IT strives to keep your personal information accurately recorded. We have implemented technology and processes to help maintain data accuracy. Completely IT provides individuals with reasonable access to personal information that they provided to Completely IT and the ability to review and correct it, as applicable. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity, such as requiring a password and user ID, before granting access to your data. To view and change the personal information that you directly provided to Completely IT you can return to the TeamSideline Profile page and follow the instructions on that TeamSideline Web page. 

**8\. Keeping Your Information Secure**  
Completely IT takes seriously the trust you place in us. To prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, to maintain data accuracy, and to ensure the appropriate use of the information, Completely IT utilizes appropriate physical, technical and administrative procedures to safeguard the information we collect. 

**9\. Contacting Us**  
We value your opinions. If you have comments or questions about our privacy statement, please send them to the Completely IT using the TeamSideline Contact us Web page or write to us at the following address: 

Completely IT   
Privacy Mailbox   
P.O. Box 3081  
Rocklin, CA 95677

Rev. March 2010
